[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Normal saline solution contains this percentage of salt (NaCl)?", "correct_answer": "0.9%", "incorrect_answers": ["9%", "4.5%", "1.3%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film is memorable for this quote?\nNow back up, put the gun down, and get me a pack of Tropical Fruit Bubblicious.", "correct_answer": "Bad Boys", "incorrect_answers": ["National Security", "Bad Boys II", "Blue Streak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Matt Murdock, Daredevils alter ego, is deaf.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Having won 6 Tony Awards, including Best Musical, this 1950s production is a modern retelling of the Faust legend. Its main characters are Mr. Applegate, Joe Boyd and Lola.", "correct_answer": "Damn Yankees", "incorrect_answers": ["Hello, Dolly!", "The Music Man", "Guys and Dolls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous Greek philosopher tutored Alexander the Great and stimulated his interest in science, medicine, philosophy and literature?", "correct_answer": "Aristotle", "incorrect_answers": ["Plato", "Socrates", "Epicurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what type of plant does Rockys buddy, Paulie, work in the 1976 movie Rocky?", "correct_answer": "Meat-packing plant", "incorrect_answers": ["Diapers plant", "Weaponry plant", "Candy plant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1985 animated feature film version of the anime classic Fist of the North Star, what character defeats Shin?", "correct_answer": "Raoh", "incorrect_answers": ["Kenshiro", "Rei", "Ken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Didaskaleinophobia is the fear of animals that have rabies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedy, written and directed by John Hughes, starred an actor who was nominated for a Golden Globe.", "correct_answer": "Ferris Buellers Day Off", "incorrect_answers": ["Home Alone", "3 Men and a Baby", "National Lampoons Vacation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the popular TV show The Honeymooners, Ralph worked as a bus driver for this fictional company.", "correct_answer": "Gotham Bus Company", "incorrect_answers": ["Cityline Bus Company", "Red and Tan Bus Company", "Metro Bus Company"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the first popular WWW browser. Microsofts Internet Explorer is also based on it.", "correct_answer": "NCSA Mosaic", "incorrect_answers": ["Opera", "lynx", "Netscape Navigator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A cells life cycle is the series of changes the cell goes through from the time it is formed until it reproduces itself. It includes two stages. What are these two stages?", "correct_answer": "Cell division and interphase", "incorrect_answers": ["Interphase and cytokinesis", "Cytokinesis and mitosis", "Mitosis and meiosis"]}]